geekchamp.com 2013-03-13

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains our privacy practices for WindowsPhoneGeek.com and all other services provided by WPGeek Ltd (“WPGeek”). Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

Your use of the WindowsPhoneGeek.com web site, domain name and all other services provided by WPGeek, indicates your agreement to the Privacy Policy laid out below.

**1.INFORMATION COLLECTED AND RECEIVED**

What information we collect and why we collect it:

  * Your name, email address and other information that you enter are collected when you register with us. By registering with us, you consent to the use of your Personal Information as indicated in this policy.
  * WPGeek uses PayPal for all payments performed via the web site. Your credit card number, bank account, and other financial information is not revealed to us by PayPal. (We recommend that you read their privacy policy.)
  * You may update your Personal Information at any time by logging-in and going to your profile.

WPGeek automatically receives and records some information from your browser when you visit the site, such as your IP address, cookies and data about which pages you visit on the site through the use of log files provided by our third-party tracking-utility partners. This information helps us analyze and understand how the site works for members and visitors.

We collect information about the use of our website. We analyze this data to determine what is of interest to our customers, and thereby improve our service.

**Cookies:**

** ** WPGeek uses cookies to help you personalize your online experience with the Site. A Cookie is a small text file that is placed and stored on your hard disk by a web server. The cookies used by the Site are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies do not contain your personal information and do not retrieve any information from your personal computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies, but you will still be able to access most of the Site.

Our partners or third-party service providers may also use cookies on the Site or on their website. We have no control over these cookies and this privacy statement covers the use of cookies by WPGeek only and does not cover the use of cookies by partners or third parties. You should review the privacy policy of any third-party web site that you visit as a result of an advert or link on the Site.

**2\. DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

WPGeek will not sell or disclose your name, email address or other personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this policy. Your WPGeek account Personal Information is protected by the password you have chosen for your privacy and security. WPGeek uses the information described in this policy to provide and improve our services and products, for billing, for identification and authentication purposes, to contact members or interested parties, and for general research and aggregate reporting.

WPGeek will not give, sell or exchange any personal information about you to a third party unless required to do so by law.

**3.** **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**

All linked sites on WindowsPhoneGeek.com are not under WPGeek`s control and WPGeek is not responsible for the content of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site, or any changes or updates to such sites. You acknowledge that WPGeek provides the links to you only as a convenience and it does not endorse the linked sites or their use or content.

**4.CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

WPGeek reserves the right to change the terms of this privacy policy from time to time. The new policy will be considered active immediately upon posting of changes on the Site.

**5\. OTHER**

WPGeek`s Terms of Use require all account owners to be at least 18 years of age (or have the permission and supervision of a responsible parent or legal guardian), therefore, this policy does not discuss use of our site or services by minors.

Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
